stateofsearch.com 2019-06-04

# Privacy Policy - State of Digital

We want to protect your privacy, this policy applies to personal information collected on the State of Digital website or any sites owned or managed by UnGagged Ltd. These terms explain how we will use any personal information we collect or you provide through our websites.

We comply with data protection legislation such as the Data Protection Act 1998. This regulates the processing of personal data relating to you and grants you various rights in respect of your personal data.

## **What information do we collect?**

We collect certain types of personal information when you register for an State of Digital event or fill in a form or signup for our newsletter. This information may include your name, address and email address.

When you browse our site, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any third parties unless we have specifically obtained your permission to do so beforehand.

## **Consent**

_How do you get my consent?_

When you provide us with personal information to complete place an order or fill in a form, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

_How do I withdraw my consent?_

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or mailing us UnGagged Ltd., Technology House, 151 Silbury Blvd, Milton Keynes, MK9 1LH, UK

## **What do we do with your information?**

The personal information you provide us may be used to:

  * Send you emails about our conferences and other updates
  * Send you information from State of Digital that we think you’ll be interested in
  * Send you information from our advertisers
  * Target advertising based on your interests, if you’ve provided those

## **Third-Party Services**

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

## **Security**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

**COOKIES**

The State of Digital website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.

## **Policy Changes, Questions & Comments**

We’ll reserve the right to modify this privacy policy, changes will be posted on this page and will take immediate effect on posting. 

If our business is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to market State of Digital to you.  
If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, the request should be emailed to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or sent to our offices at Technology House, 151 Silbury Blvd, Milton Keynes, MK9 1LH, UK.
